Alex@What type do you like?
Megan@Gentle and refined
Megan@A gentleman
Megan@Can play the piano
Megan@Speaks English
Megan@Can't be weaker than me
Alex@Your standards are really high
Alex@Single since birth
Megan@Hey, you can't say that
Megan@At least they should be better than me in these aspects
Alex@Alright, be careful
Alex@Don't slip
Megan@The water is still so cold
Megan@Wait a moment
Megan@It's freezing
Megan@It's really cold
Megan@You're grabbing again
Megan@You like grabbing so much
Megan@You have your own
Alex@Isn't it too hot?
Megan@No
Megan@You're using it comfortably
Alex@What are you saying?
Megan@Girls are more considerate than guys
Alex@Right?
Alex@You like what? Gentle and refined?
Alex@Girls can be like that too, you know
Alex@I want to bite this butt
Megan@Pervert
Alex@No wonder you're so innocent since birth
Megan@Hey, that's being lustful
Alex@But lust is human nature, haha
Alex@Seeing a beautiful woman makes you lustful
Megan@Pervert
Megan@Flirt
Alex@Being attracted to women is natural
Megan@I can't stand you
Alex@I'm only like this with you, okay?
Alex@Really, hmm
Megan@Yeah, right
Megan@You flirt with everyone
Megan@Rinse yourself
Alex@So stingy
Alex@It's just a quick rinse
Alex@Be careful not to catch a cold
Alex@Here's the towel